<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Saksham Arora</title>
        <link>http://sakshamarora1.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Saksham Arora</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>sakshamarora1001@gmail.com (Saksham Arora)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>sakshamarora1001@gmail.com (Saksham Arora)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:52:33 &#43;0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://sakshamarora1.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>My GSoC 2020 Journey</title>
    <link>http://sakshamarora1.github.io/2020/09/mygsocjourneyandtips/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:52:33 &#43;0530</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://sakshamarora1.github.io/2020/09/mygsocjourneyandtips/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I have been a student developer under Python Software Foundation for the last 4 months as a part of Google Summer of Code program and have successfully completed the program on 31st August 2020, the last day for this year’s program! So, for the unacquainted — What is Google Summer of Code (GSoC)?
Well, It is an annual program in which university students all around the globe contribute to open source during their break from school in the summer(starting from April/May and ending in August).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>GSoC Final Report</title>
    <link>http://sakshamarora1.github.io/2020/08/gsocfinalreport/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 16:52:33 &#43;0530</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://sakshamarora1.github.io/2020/08/gsocfinalreport/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Google Summer of Code 2020 Final Work Submission Report  Name: Saksham Arora Organisation: Python Software Foundation Sub-Organisation: DFFML - DataFlow Facilitator for Machine Learning Project: Integrating Image Processing into DFFML Proposal: https://blogs.python-gsoc.org/media/proposals/GSoC_2020_Proposal_DFFML_-_PSF.pdf  Aim Add ways of training and testing machine learning models in DFFML on image datasets and perform image processing and computer vision tasks via DFFML.
The project is divided into 2 parts:
 Wrapping the image processing libraries namely OpenCV and Scikit-Image.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>First blog</title>
    <link>http://sakshamarora1.github.io/2020/05/firstblog/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 03:15:31 &#43;0530</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://sakshamarora1.github.io/2020/05/firstblog/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Work in Progress! I have created this website using the hugo static website generator https://gohugo.io/ and is still a work in progress! : D I am currently using the LoveIt theme https://themes.gohugo.io/loveit/ by Dillon
I will be documenting my GSoC'2020 journey and adding descriptions about my projects in the coming weeks!
I have also been posting GSoC related blogs on https://blogs.python-gsoc.org/en/sakshamaroras-blog, you can check them out!]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
